rewardscentral.com.au 2019-03-06

# Privacy Policy - RewardsCentral

Privacy Policy

##### RewardsCentral understands that you are concerned about your privacy. That's why RewardsCentral has created this privacy and permission statement, to demonstrate our firm commitment to your privacy.

##### How does RewardsCentral use the information I provide in the Account Settings and Rewards Profile?

RewardsCentral uses the information you provide in your Account Settings and Rewards Profile to target and personalise the emails, surveys and letters we send to you and the offers we make available to you. We do this to ensure that you only receive relevant and appropriate information.

Demographic and profile data is only shared with RewardsCentral clients and advertisers on an aggregate or collective basis. For example, we might tell our clients that 3680 of our members live in a particular town or suburb, or that 43% of our members have indicated an interest in sport.

Your personally identifiable information such as your name, address or email address will never be sold to any third party. Your personally identifiable information may be shared with a third party if it is required by law. Your personally identifiable information may also be shared with a third party (for example a supplier or partner of ours) if it is necessary for us to process a transaction that you request, or if you opt-in to a service or feature where we outsource some aspects of the provision of that service or feature. For example, if you opt in to the Postal Rewards feature, we may share your postal address with a mail processing company that sends mail to you on our behalf. We have strict legal agreements in place that prevent any third party from using that information more than once, or for any purpose beyond what is allowed for in the agreement.

##### What happens to the answers I give in an online survey?

RewardsCentral follows strict market research guidelines that govern what happens to the answers that you give when participating in an online survey. The results of online surveys (where you are invited to participate in the survey by email) are only used for market research analysis. The information you give in these online surveys is not used to target direct marketing messages. You can be assured that any information you provide in an online survey is kept absolutely confidential.

##### What about security?

RewardsCentral has modern and robust security measures in place to protect the information you give to us from loss, misuse and alteration. We are constantly reviewing and upgrading these security measures to ensure the very best of protection to you.

##### Why does RewardsCentral record IP Addresses?

When a user joins RewardsCentral, our computers may record their IP address. In the event that we detect fraud or abuse of our program or our Web site and computers, we may use the IP address of the offender to take action against them. Ultimately this ensures greater protection for you and your personal information.

##### What are cookies and why does RewardsCentral use them?

A cookie is a piece of data stored on a user's computer hard drive, containing information about that user. A cookie can only be accessed across the Internet by the Web site that placed it there. Cookies are used by the RewardsCentral web site to enable web site sign in, and to track the source of new members joining the web site. The use of cookies in this way is wide-spread and commonly accepted by the Internet community. 

RewardsCentral also uses cookies (including third-party cookies) to correlate a RewardsCentral member with their visits to other web sites containing online ads, and this data is then used to enhance the selection process when inviting users to participate in a survey or receive advertising offers on the web site or via email. For example, a RewardsCentral or third party cookie may track and correlate a user's RewardsCentral ID number together with that member's visit to other web sites containing online ads. This data would then be used to enhance the selection process when inviting users to participate in a survey about those ads. In all instances, cookies used by RewardsCentral would not contain personally identifiable information such as your name or email address.

You may choose to reject a cookie that the RewardsCentral Web site attempts to place on your computer, however you may then be limited in your use of some areas of the Web site.

##### What about other Web sites?

The RewardsCentral Web site contains links to other Web sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of these other Web sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our Web site and to read the privacy statements of other Web sites that you use. This privacy statement applies only to Web sites owned and operated by RewardsCentral Australia Pty Ltd.

##### What is "spam" and does RewardsCentral send it?

The widely accepted definition of "spam" is unsolicited commercial email, or in other words, email of a commercial nature that the recipient does not want. **RewardsCentral does not send "spam".** This is because when you join RewardsCentral, you must expressly agree to allow us to send to you commercial advertising email.

##### How many emails will I receive?

We respect your time and attention. We will never send to you more than fourteen advertising emails per week. That is a guarantee.

##### How can I stop RewardsCentral from sending me email?

Each email we send to you contains a link at the very bottom allowing you to unsubscribe.

To unsubscribe now, click here.

**If you have received unwanted email sent from RewardsCentral,** or purporting to be sent from RewardsCentral, please contact RewardsCentral.

**If you have any questions** about the privacy and permission practices of the RewardsCentral Web site or your dealings with RewardsCentral Australia Pty Ltd, please contact RewardsCentral. We are committed to being of service to you and resolving any issues that may arise.

This statement should be read in conjunction with the RewardsCentral Terms of Service.
